your business is open to serve your
customers we open our doors every day to
serve their needs are we ready however
to open our doors for our employees and
their times of need people are
undoubtedly any company's most valuable
asset
they provide the ideas the skills and
the commitment to make our businesses
thrive they fulfill their jobs through
dedicated service to our customers and
to the institution but as human beings
we are all constantly faced with in
certainties our employees may fall ill
meat accidents or even passed away thus
affecting our livelihood of your
families and dependents
when these happen will the employer be
able to provide help to its worker
inmate life insurance coverage may be
one of the most important benefits that
a company or organization can provide to
its employees or members with group life
insurance you are able to offer
financial security to your people
without any burden to your company life
insurance is a basic necessity for
everyone however many of us are not
capable of acquiring a coverage that
would be sufficient for our families in
times of uncertainties
during this times ordinary employees
specially may just have their little
savings to depend on plus whatever help
they can get from their employers as
employers on the other hand we strive to
provide our people with the right
benefits to support their various needs
and one of this very important benefits
is group life insurance having this
assures our people that we are genuinely
concerned for their welfare and that we
appreciate their dedication to the
organization knowing that they are
covered with group life insurance
greatly helps in boosting their morale
promoting loyalty to the company and
increasing their productivity with this
financial protection employees know that
their employers truly care for them
providing efficient group life and
health insurance to various institutions
is a commitment of sunlight grapa
financial born out of a solid
partnership between two financial Giants
Sonlight prepa financial incorporating
carries a distinct mark of global
excellence rooted and Filipino values
parent company Sun Life Financial and
the Yushchenko group of companies have
both served millions of people for more
than a century today
sunlight grandpa has become one of the
leading life insurers in the country its
group life and health portfolio includes
physicists in the industries of banking
and finance manufacturing construction
engineering and real estate be a khadeem
health care government institutions and
Business Process Outsourcing Sun Life
Breakfast group yearly renewable term
insurance is a pure protection plan for
employees additional writers may be
included to the plan in order to
maximize the benefits that the employees
can receive in case of accident
disability and dismemberment critical
illness terminal illness hospitalization
and surgical procedures as well as
hospital income Sun Life Breakfast group
credit life insurance and group mortgage
redemption assurance on the other hand
cover the short and long term loans
being issued by lending companies
these insurance coverage protect both
the creditor and the tetras family in
case of borrower passes away during the
payment period through these insurance
coverages possible legal infant Venus's
are avoided and both creditor and debtor
are benefited in terms of peace of mind
and goodwill sunlight grapa Financial is
founded on the strong synergy between
Sun Life and the tranquil group to
better serve Filipinos in their
financial protection needs each and
every member of our organization
contributes the realization of this goal
our employees and sales team are
provided with exceptional training and
development opportunities and a
recognized for their professionalism and
passion to excel sunlight preppers
access to the state-of-the-art
technology and product delivery
capabilities further enhance the
customer's experience we at Sun Life
grab a financial are open in helping you
create an effective group life and
health program with maximize benefits at
reasonable cost taking into
consideration the specialized needs of
your organization it is our goal to
bring financial literacy to our society
and empower individuals and institutions
to attain financial freedom this is our
passion for life